{
	"quiz": [
		{
			"question": "API",
			"answer": "Application Programming Interface"
		},
		{
			"question": "CMS",
			"answer": "Content Management System"
		},
		{
			"question": "DNS",
			"answer": "Domain Name Service"
		},
		{
			"question": "FTP",
			"answer": "File Transfer Protocol"
		},
		{
			"question": "ISP",
			"answer": "Internet Service Provider"
		}
		,
		{
			"question": "LAN",
			"answer": "Local Area Network"
		}
		,
		{
			"question": "SEM",
			"answer": "Search Engine Marketing"
		}
		,
		{
			"question": "SEO",
			"answer": "Search Engine Optimization"
		}
		,
		{
			"question": "UI",
			"answer": "User Interface"
		},
		{
			"question": "UX",
			"answer": "User Experience"
		}
	]
}